It sure isn't easy getting
into a big company...
Job Listings
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
An environment to grow alongside
your students at a historic institution
Yumegokoroha Private High School
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Would you like to lend your support in helping students spread their wings? A fulfilling
environment where teachers can pursue their work style of choice! Let's build tradition together.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
[Job Description]
We encourage those interested to apply quickly!
Job Responsibilities
Course instruction
Student guidance
Lesson preparation/exam grading
See more
A teaching job?
Huh?
Shiranui Private High School
Shiranui Private High School?
Mr. Hitoma...
Episode 11
The Misanthrope and the Nigh Past
Social Studies Prep Room
Excuse me.
Mr. Hitoma, are you here?
I've brought the notebooks
for world history.
Oh, thanks.
Wait, huh? Haruna?
Yeah, Mirai Haruna.
Still don't remember my name?
No, I remember
That's not it. Wasn't Akazawa
on class duty today?
Rio had to go somewhere after school.
I'm filling in for her.
Didn't something similar happen before?
You mean the time with the committee?
Or the group assignment?
That's way too many times.
Still, I kind of like it
when people ask me for help.
Haruna, you can be strange sometimes.
That's not true.
Homework for you.
What?
Have someone help you out by next week.
Do I need to do it, or else?
No, not at all.
Huh?
It's just that I worry a little about you.
Feel free to ignore the deadline, too.
You're a weird teacher.
Do you mean that like when they say,
"You're a funny girl?"
Huh?
I'm sorry.
If I really had a problem,
I think you're the last one I'd go to.
That's fine by me.
As a teacher, it's not like
I'll always be around for you.
How irresponsible.
What do you want?
That's just how it works.
That's why I want you to learn all
the tricks to living life all by yourself.
I'll be just fine by myself.
That's what everyone thinks at first.
So you used to think that way, too?
Nope.
I quickly gave up on that
to depend on others all the time.
Life's easy when other people help you.
And they get to feel good about it,
so it's a win-win situation.
Isn't it great?
You're a weird teacher.
Rio, good morning!
Good morning, Mirai!
I gave the world history notebooks
to Mr. Hitoma yesterday.
Oh, thanks! You're the best!
No, it's fine.
Anything for you, Rio.
Oh, yeah.
Can you do one more thing
for me while you're at it?
Yeah, sure.
Awesome!
Love you, Mirai!
Social Studies Prep Room
Mr. Hitoma, are you what
people call an otaku?
Well, strictly speaking,
I wouldn't say that exactly,
but under a more general
definition of "otaku"...
I suppose that might not be
an entirely untrue statement...
So, which is it?
Sorry. I'm an otaku.
Gross.
Don't say that
after taking the time to ask!
I'm kidding.
You're not that gross, Mr. Hitoma.
Does that mean I am a little bit?
Kind of?
Oh, forget I asked.
Anyway, Haruna.
You filled in this class
journal, didn't you?
The name says Rio Akazawa,
but this is your handwriting.
Wow, Rio's handwriting
looks just like mine!
This is your writing style as well.
Wait, you can tell the difference?
I'm not that stupid, you know.
Did she make you do this again?
She just asked me for a favor.
Well, keep it to a minimum.
It doesn't do Akazawa any good.
Okay, class is about to start.
Get going.
Sure.
Hey, Mirai, are you friendly with Hitoma?
Not particularly. Why?
You're always off to
the social studies prep room.
They have books that aren't
at the school library.
Except Mr. Hitoma's there to annoy you.
Do you have a thing for Hitoma?
Ugh, no!
I know, Mirai.
Wanna skip our next
history class together?
What?
By pretending to go to the nurse.
I don't know about that...
Even if I ask as a favor?
It's bad to ditch class...
You wanna listen to Hitoma's lecture?
What?
So boring.
Being with you is boring now, Mirai.
Social Studies Prep Room
School is kind of like jail.
That's a wild comparison.
A place where people
who just happen to be similar ages
gather at a predetermined time to be
educated for a predetermined period.
And sometimes they make you
participate in groups.
You don't like doing group work?
I'd say that most people don't.
Guess you're right.
Not gonna tell me off?
For what?
I mean, I should be in class now.
We've got an escaped prisoner here.
You're the only one who'd joke like that.
Maybe so.
So? Not gonna yell at me?
I've been here every day lately.
It's fine if sometimes,
you just don't feel like it.
And this is a free period for me.
That makes you my partner in crime.
Nuh-uh! I'm preparing for my next class!
What's that?
Kind of like lesson prep
and a cheat sheet in one.
Hey, Mr. Hitoma.
What would you do if the
world was going to end?
Where'd that come from?
Just a what-if.
Let me think.
I'd beat all the games
I never got around to.
Seriously?
It's important to me.
Even with the world ending?
Wouldn't you normally choose to spend it
with your girlfriend or your family?
Is that what you'd pick, Haruna?
I think... I would lie.
Lie?
Yeah.
I'd lie and say, "There's no way
the world's going to end."
And I'd spend my last moments living
normally with the people who believed me.
How kind of you.
Huh?
I mean, aren't you lying for those
who can't accept that it's all ending?
I'm just dragging them along with me.
Since I'm the one who can't accept it.
I wish the world would end tomorrow...
If you told me, "There's no way
the world's going to end,"
I think that I'd believe you.
What?
But then you can't play video games.
I guess not.
It's fine, though.
What's that mean?
I wasn't trying to drag you
into it, Mr. Hitoma.
So you don't have to believe me.
I don't care if you fool me.
It's fine if you lie,
so tell me what's on your mind.
I'm on your side, Haruna.
Hey...
Is it okay... for me to stay here?
Yeah.
Like I said, Mr. Hitoma...
Let's be adults about this.
And by adults, you mean?
Teaching's a business, too.
Do you understand your obligations
as an employee of this school?
And you know how much the Akazawa
family contributes in donations.
Well, yes.
In that case...
You know what the right
move is, don't you?
Pretend the bullying didn't happen?
Oh, you make me sound
like the bad guy.
There's no proof
that Akazawa did it, is there?
It'd be nothing but a losing fight.
So think about whose side you
should take for your benefit.
My benefit?
You've got a long life ahead.
Think about your career.
You're a bright man, Mr. Hitoma.
You'll make the smart decision, won't you?
I can't do it.
I can't stay quiet about it.
I made a promise to Haruna.
I'll be her ally to the end.
Mr. Hitoma.
Being someone's ally
also means making enemies.
I'm well aware.
Hold on.
Are you in that kind of
relationship with Haruna?
Huh?!
I hear Haruna visits the social
studies prep room quite often.
What's she's been getting up to?
I've just been giving her advice.
Say what you will about me,
but don't insult Haruna like that.
Sure, fine.
You've made your intentions
very clear, Mr. Hitoma.
Ill-advised as they may be.
It's too bad, Mr. Hitoma.
Principal's Office
Mr. Hitoma.
Surely you know why I've called you here.
No. What is it, Vice Principal?
That's enough playing dumb.
It seems you've been physically
disciplining Mirai Haruna.
What?
Haruna's been covered
in fresh bruises lately,
and there are records of her being
treated in the nurse's office.
They must have been
from your corporal punishment.
You're wrong! I've done
nothing of the sort!
We have testimony on hand.
You were physically abusing her
in the social studies prep room.
What?
And to retaliate,
Haruna was bullying Akazawa.
You're mistaken!
Haruna was the one being bullied—
There's no point making excuses!
Haruna and Akazawa told us all about it!
What? Haruna did?
You will be suspended
for the foreseeable future.
You are not to make contact
with Haruna or Akazawa.
Is that understood?'
Haruna was expelled from school
for disorderly conduct.
I was forced into resigning as a teacher.
Haruna.
So you were here.
It's been a while.
Um... are you doing well?
Oh, are you eating properly?
Getting sleep?
Just kidding.
I pull a lot of all-nighters,
so I can't speak...
Shut up...
Didn't you say you'd
believe me, even if I lied?
This is all your fault.
I'm the one who lied
about the physical abuse.
You were being a real hassle...
So I figured I'd drag you into it...
But you... still believed
my lies, didn't you?
Is this because I tried to step in?
That's right! It's all...
your fault for taking my complaints
seriously and trying to do the impossible!
It's my fault.
It's my fault that you...
That's right.
That's why, Mr. Hitoma...
You got what you deserved.
It's all my fault.
Oh, crap!
I'm gonna be late!
Morning, Mr. Hitoma...
Good morning, Ms. Karasuma.
Wow, you're pale as a ghost.
I'm a little sleep-deprived...
Wanna rest in my office
until the all-school morning assembly?
Maybe I will...
Wow! These bottles are so cute!
These bottles are unique to our school.
Oh, good morning, Haruka, Mr. Hitoma.
Mr. Hitoma?
Good morning, Yuki.
Is she the new teacher?
Yes!
She's our brand new hire, who just
graduated from a women's college in Tokyo.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the brand new hire, Mirai Haruna.
I hope to learn a lot
from you working together!
Hey there.
I'm Haruka Karasuma, the school nurse.
And this is...
It's been ages, Mr. Hitoma.
Mr. Hitoma, Ms. Haruna.
Do you two know each other?
Huh? Well...
Yes, actually, we do!
Mr. Hitoma was my homeroom
teacher back in high school.
And now you're teaching
at the same school?
As homeroom and assistant
homeroom teacher!
It must be fate!
Fate?
It's basically the same for you, Yuki.
You went after Satoru, your homeroom
teacher, and ended up at the same school.
Is that story true?
Now I'm curious!
I'd love to hear all about it!
What?!
It's finally your first day.
Think you'll be all right?
Yes!
I was surprised at first when
I learned the truth about this school,
but I'm totally fine now.
I'm sure there's plenty more
to surprise you,
but you'll be okay with Mr. Hitoma here.
What?
Yes!
I'll have Mr. Hitoma show me the ropes!
Break a leg, Ms. Haruna!
Thank you very much!
My first class... I'm nervous.
Well, the first day's only introductions.
Don't stress so much, and take it easy.
Were you nervous on your
first day, Mr. Hitoma?
Ah...
I totally forgot how it went.
Wow.
So you really were able to take it easy.
Nope.
I was so nervous,
I can't remember any of it.
Haruna.
I'm really sorry about back then.
You were in a tough situation,
and I made it worse by stepping in.
Mr. Hitoma.
It's all right.
I was young back then.
Haruna...
So it's not your fault.
Why don't we forget about that?
We're both adults now. Okay?
If you say so, Haruna.
What's done is done,
so let's put it behind us.
Let's work hard together
as colleagues from now on!
I look forward to working
with you, Ms. Haruna.
I do, too, Mr. Hitoma.
Advanced Class
This is the advanced class,
which we're in charge of.
We have six students.
Two of them are new faces
who just moved up this year.
I said, don't be nervous.
Things will go the way they do.
Yes!
Okay, here we go.
Prince Waka!
Look this way!
Shoot me in the heart!
Thanks for winking at us!
Oh, Mr. Rei!
It's great to finally see you again!
I love you today, too!
What exactly... is going on here?
This is a makeshift fashion show runway.
Would you care to join me, Hitoma?
Hitoma?
Don't climb up on the desks!
And let's address the teachers properly.
I do apologize if my actions offended you.
That being said, there's only one
person I want to address with a title.
You're blushing!
Not used to this kinda stuff?
This new teacher seems like a pushover!
She looks like a child,
and even less reliable than Hitoma.
But she just screams "new teacher,"
which I find adorable.
There really was plenty more
to surprise me.
Looks like it's gonna
be another tough year.
Next Episode:
The Misanthrope and Falsehood Found Nigh